camdolls.com 2017-09-30

# Camdolls - Privacy policy

Last modified: October 9, 2012

## We consider the privacy of its users to be a serious issue.

Please read this Privacy Policy (the "Policy") carefully. By accessing or using Our website, You acknowledge that You have read, understand and agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy on this Website. If You do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Website. It is Your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, so We encourage You to visit this page often. 

In order to facilitate Your reading, here is an outline of the Policy: 

  1. Preliminary Provisions
  2. Special Consideration regarding minors
  3. Account Membership
  4. Your Information
  5. Disclosure of Your information
  6. Other Websites
  7. Access or change Your information
  8. Information Security
  9. Information Location
  10. Contacting Us

## 1 PRELIMINARY PROVISIONS

1.1 Party Definitions – The operative parties referred to in this Agreement are defined as follows: 

1.1.1 Us – The term “We” as well as all first-person pronouns (Us, Our, Ours), these provisions are referring to the administrators of the Camdolls Website. Additionally, when the terms “Site” or “Website” are used, these terms refer to Camdolls, any predecessor or successor domain or URL, along with any website published by Us, or website we may choose to operate in the future, unless a site is specifically exempt from this Agreement. 

1.1.2 You, the User - As the User of this Site and/or Services, this Policy will refer to the User as “You” or through any second-person pronouns, such as “Yours,” etc. Hereinafter, the User of the Site and/or Services shall be referred to in applicable second-person pronouns. You certify that You are over eighteen (18) years of age. 

1.1.3 User vs. Member - For the purposes of this Policy, all Members are Users, but not all Users are Members. This Policy applies to all Users whether they are Members or not. You become a User by accessing this Site or the Services in any way, therefore You need not become a Member of the Site to make this Policy apply to You. You are not considered a Member as defined by this Policy until such time as You have submitted Your online account Registration (hereinafter “Registration”). You become a Member by registering on the Site with id.net for a User ID and password as required by the Registration, as discussed below. 

1.2 What this Policy is – This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices of Camdolls regarding any personal data You may provide to Us or that We receive from You. We remind You that by accessing the Site in any manner, You are affirmatively agreeing to being bound by all of the terms contained in this Policy. 

##  2 SPECIAL CONSIDERATION REGARDING MINORS – THIS SERVICE IS FOR ADULTS ONLY! 

2.1 In order to use the Site or any Services provided by Us, You must have attained the age of majority in Your jurisdiction (the “Age of Majority” ). You represent and warrant You are at least eighteen (18) or twenty-one (21) years of age, depending on the Age of Majority in Your jurisdiction, and that You have the legal capacity to enter into this Agreement. If You are not at least eighteen (18) or twenty-one (21) years of age, depending on the Age of Majority in Your jurisdiction, You must exit the Site immediately and may not use or access the Site or use the Services in any manner. 

2.2 We specifically disclaim any responsibility or liability for any misrepresentations regarding a User’s age. 

##  3 ACCOUNT MEMBERSHIP 

3.1 Although much of the Site is available without creating an account, to access certain features of the Site and Services, You must register as a Member of the Site. 

3.2 Member Login – We use the services of id.net as a login system. You must link one of Your id.net identities to Our Website, since this is now the only way to login to Our Site. 

3.3 KYC Policy – Some of Our features and services will require You to login with an id.net identity that is verified. In other words, Your id.net account should have gone through a KYC verification process undertaken by id.net to this effect. You should have also chosen to benefit the id.net identity linked to Our Website from this verified status. Only Members that wish to access those particular features and services will need to have a verified id.net identity linked to Our Website. 

##  4 YOUR INFORMATION 

4.1 The information that We receive includes sets of information: Your information and the information We receive about You. 

4.1.1 Your information means the information entered when You fill out forms on Our Site, when You proceed to registration on Our Site via id.net. It includes first and last name, address as well as zip code, email address, telephone number, authentication data, age, company, country. Your information can be either administered by id.net regarding Your id.net identity linked to Our Website, or administered by Us regarding your profile on Our Website. Collection of Your information may also occur when You ask a question, complete a form, access certain areas of Our Site, or send Us an email. 

4.1.2 The information We receive about You means: 

4.1.2.1 Non-personal information: 

  * Data in relation to the use of the Website, such as the date and time You visit the Website, the web address or URL You are on
  * Data in relation to the Website services and activities

4.1.2.2 Technical information, including: 

  * IP address
  * Browser
  * Operating system You use
  * If You are logged into id.net, Your User ID and the email of Your main Id.net profile.

4.2 How We use Your information 

4.2.1 Any information we receive regarding You is to enable Us to offer better services to You. We use Your information to complete transactions, respond to Your requests, answer Your questions, and notify You of promotions updates, or special offers that We think may interest You. 

4.2.2 We also use Your information for optimizing the operation of the Site, enhancing Our promotional and marketing activities, improvement of Our products and services, troubleshooting, performing administrative tasks, handling of disputes, enforcing Our agreements, complying with laws and regulations, cooperation with law enforcement activities, and for other purposes necessary to provide You with the services You requested. 

4.2.3 You may choose not to provide Us with certain information. Although be aware that, this will affect Your access to Our features and Our ability to provide You with certain services. 

4.2.4 Take notice that If You use Our Site or a link to Our Site to send information about a product or service to another person, We may collect and store Your information and the information of any recipient. We may use the recipient’s information to allow him or her to view or access the information We provide You upon Your request. 

4.3 How We use the information We receive 

4.3.1 Every time You visit the Site, We receive and record information on Our server logs from Your browser, Your IP address, cookie information, and reference site domain name. 

4.3.2 Information We receive about You help Us locate Our users, determine high traffic areas and enhance the analysis of communication tools. As part of that ongoing analysis, We may use devices called “web beacons” to help Us know when You receive and read the emails We send You, as well as cookies to improve Our site and facilitate its use. 

4.3.3 We may install both persistent and session cookies when You visit Our Site. Cookies allow Us to recognize users and avoid repetitive requests for the same information. If You choose to reject all cookies, there are areas of the Site that may not function properly. 

## 5 DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

5.1 Privacy Settings for Your profile – You can control the information of Your profile, You want to be accessible to Members or Users. There are three levels of information disclosure, which are the following: 

5.1.1 _Private_ – this means that You are on a one on one stream, and only the Member You are interacting with can see some of Your information that is displayed on Our Website. 

5.1.2 _Friends Only_ – this means that You can socially interact and stream with Members You have defined as “Friends”, and only those Members can view Your information that is displayed on Our Website and contact You. 

5.1.3 _Public_ – this means that all Your information displayed on Your profile and Your stream, can be seen by Users. In other words, this information can be associated with You, can show up when someone does a research on Our Website or a public search engine and will be accessible to everyone who uses Our APIs.   
**Take notice that by setting Your streams to “Public”, all Your streams will be accessible and viewed by Users.**

5.2 Except in the event that you have willingly chosen to do so, We do not share Your information with other companies, organizations and individuals outside of the Company unless one of the following circumstances apply: 

5.2.1 With Your consent – We will share Your information to other companies, organizations and individuals outside of the Company when We have Your consent to do so. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any personal information. 

5.2.2 For external processing – We provide Your information to Our affiliates or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for Us, based on Our instructions and in compliance with Our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidential and security measures. 

5.2.3 For legal reasons – We will share Your information with other companies, organizations or individuals, outside the Company, if We have a good-faith belief that access, use , preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to: 

  * meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request (including legal requests from jurisdictions outside of Hong Kong) 
  * enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations 
  * detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues 
  * protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of the Website, Our Users or the public as required or permitted by law. 

5.2.4 If We are involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, We will continue to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information and give affected Users notice before personal information is transferred or becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

## 6 OTHER WEBSITES

6.1 Third party login system id.net 

6.1.1 We offer You the opportunity to login to Our Website through the use of Your id.net identity linked to Our Website. Only Your information about Your id.net identity linked to Our Website, such as Your nickname, and Your email from Your id.net account will be sent to Us when You use it to register or login. We do not have access or receive any information about Your id.net account without Your consent. 

6.1.2 In order to have access to some of Our features and services, You must have a verified id.net identity linked to Our Website. In other words, Your id.net account should have gone through a KYC verification process undertaken by id.net to this effect. You should have also chosen to benefit the id.net identity linked to Our Website from this verified status. We will receive a third party verification from id.net, meaning that Your id.net identity linked to Our Website is certified. By proceeding this way, Your information is subject to the terms of service of the previously mentioned third party website login system. 

6.1.3 Once You delink or delete Your id.net identity linked to Our Website, We will no longer be able to access the information from the id.net identity You have chosen to login and link to Our Website. 

6.2 Links to other websites 

6.2.1 Take notice that Our Site may contain links to other sites operated by service providers, Our affiliates or other third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy policies, practices or contents of such other sites. Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy do not apply to information gathered on other sites. 

6.2.2 When You leave the Site the privacy policies and practices of that other site apply; We encourage You to be aware of them when You are on those other sites and submitting personal information. You are responsible for reviewing the privacy policies and practices of each and every site that You visit. 

## 7 YOUR PRICACY RIGHTS TO ACCESS OR CHANGE YOUR INFORMATION ANDPRIVACY SETTINGS

7.1 Once You register via id.net, You will be able to review and change most of Your Information including, but not limited to Your email address, Your city, state, ZIP or other postal code, country, Your password and Your profile. 

7.1.1 Please promptly update Your information by logging in to Your profile and following the screen prompts. We strongly urge You to change Your password periodically to help reduce the risk of unauthorized access to Your profile information. 

7.1.2 For example, any information exchange with other users may remain in their e-mail boxes, computer caches, or instant message archive. Whether You exchanged information is kept by another user is beyond the control of Our Site. Any such information retained by Us or under its control is not available to third parties except as provided in this Policy. 

7.2 As mentioned in section 5.1, You can choose as well as change Your privacy settings for Your profile. 

## 8 INFORMATION SECURITY

8.1 We work hard to protect the Website and Our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information We hold. 

8.2 In particular: 

  * We encrypt many of Our services using SSL 
  * We review Our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard against unauthorized access to systems. 
  * We restrict access to Your information to Our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for Us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations. 

8.3 Data you provide Us with will be stored on secure servers. We take all reasonable steps to ensure the safety of the data transfer in agreement with this Policy. Transmission of data via the Internet is never completely secure, thus a guarantee of data sent electronically or transmitted cannot be given. Information offered is therefore at Your own risk. 

8.4 We use a reasonably secure method to destroy personal information. 

## 9 INFORMATION LOCATION

9.1 Our Website is hosted by servers in the Netherlands. Your information may be accessed by Us or transferred to Us in the Netherlands or to Our affiliates, business partners or service providers elsewhere in the world. 

9.2 By providing Us with Your information and information We receive from You, You consent to this transfer. We will protect the privacy and security of this information according to Our Privacy Policy, regardless of where it is processed or stored. 

## 10 CONTACTING US

We are happy to receive any queries, comments, or requests You may have regarding Our Privacy Policy. Feel free and do not hesitate to use the following email to contact Us: [privacy@camdolls.com](mailto:privacy@camdolls.com)
